A Guide to the Records of the Virginia Office of the Secretary of Education, 1994; 1998-2006
Library of Virginia
- VI. Special Projects and Governor's Initiatives, 2001-2006., Extent: 17.20 cubic feet (49 boxes). (Box 89-136)
  - Subseries VI.C. The Governor's Partnership for Achieving Successful Schools (PASS), 2002-2005., Extent: 1.05 cubic feet. (Box 125-128)
    - PASS Reports, 2003-2005
      - PASS Summary Report, Academic Intervention, Year One, August 2003 (Box 127, Folder 5)
      - PASS Summary Report, Expanded Narrative, Year One, September 2003 (Box 127, Folder 5)
      - PASS First Quarter Report, Year Two 2003-04, January 2004 (Box 127, Folder 6)
      - PASS Second Quarter Report, Year Two 2003-04, March 2004 (Box 127, Folder 6)
      - PASS Third Quarter Report, Year Two, 2003-04, May 2004 (Box 127, Folder 7)
      - PASS Year-End Report, Year Two; First Quarter Report, Year Three, January 2005 (2 copies) (Box 128, Folder 1)
      - PASS Second Quarter Report, Year Three, 2004-05, March 2005 (2 copies) (Box 128, Folder 2)
      - PASS Third Quarter Report, Year Three, 2004-05, May 2005 (2 copies) (Box 128, Folder 3)
      - Report on Student Achievement in PASS and Turnaround Specialist Schools, Prepared for Governor Mark R. Warner, 28 September 2005 (2 copies) (Box 128, Folder 4)
  - Subseries VI.D. Commission to Review, Study and Reform Educational Leadership, 2002-2005., Extent: 1.05 cubic feet. (Box 128-131)
    This subseries is housed in four boxes and is divided by topic. The original order has been maintained. The 2002 Session of the General Assembly established the Commission to Review, Study and Reform Education Leadership (HJR 20/SJR 58), a two-year, 21-member commission to "review, study and reform educational leadership." The 2004 Session of the General Assembly adopted HJR 124 to continue the Commission's work. The Secretary of Education was a member of the Commission. This series includes the records of Deputy Secretary of Education Sarah Finley and includes materials on turnaround specialists, principals, school leadership, Educational Leadership Commission and State Action for Educational Leadership Project (SAELP II) grants from the Wallace-Reader's Digest Funds. Subseries contains agendas, correspondence, memorandums, presentations, notes, handouts, press releases, e-mail, reports, grants, reference materials and articles.
    - Educational Leadership Commission
      - Correspondence, 2003 (Box 128, Folder 5)
      - Commission to Review, Study and Reform Educational Leadership, HJR 20/SJR 58 (2002), 3 June 2003 Meeting (Box 128, Folder 6)
      - Commission to Review, Study and Reform Educational Leadership, HJR 20/SJR 58 (2002), 15 November 2002 Meeting (Box 128, Folder 7)
      - Commission to Review, Study and Reform Educational Leadership, HJR 20/SJR 58 (2002), 18 October 2002 Meeting (Box 128, Folder 8)
      - Commission to Review, Study and Reform Educational Leadership, HJR 20/SJR 58 (2002), 15 July 2002 Meeting (Box 129, Folder 1)
      - Commission to Review, Study and Reform Educational Leadership, HJR 20/SJR 58 (2002), 27 June 2002 Meeting (Box 129, Folder 2)
      - Commission to Review, Study and Reform Educational Leadership, HJR 20/SJR 58 (2002), 17 November 2003 Meeting (part one) (Box 129, Folder 3)
      - Commission to Review, Study and Reform Educational Leadership, HJR 20/SJR 58 (2002), 17 November 2003 Meeting (part two) (Box 129, Folder 4)
      - Commission to Review, Study and Reform Educational Leadership, HJR 20/SJR 58 (2002), 16 September 2003 Meeting (Box 129, Folder 5)
    - Principals
      - Records, 2003-2004 (part one) (Box 129, Folder 6)
      - Records, 2003-2004 (part two) (Box 130, Folder 1)
      - Records, 2003-2004 (part three) (Box 130, Folder 2)
    - Education Roundtable
      - Records, 2003 (Box 130, Folder 3)
    - Leaders Count in Virginia Schools Conference, 9-10 October 2003
      - Records, 2003 (Box 130, Folder 4)
    - State Action for Leadership Project (SALEP) II and HJR 124, 2003-2005
      - Records, 2004 (part one) (Box 130, Folder 5)
      - Records, 2004 (part two) (Box 130, Folder 6)
      - Records, 2004 (part three) (Box 131, Folder 1)
      - Records, 2004 (part four) (Box 131, Folder 2)
      - Records, 2004 (part five) (Box 131, Folder 3)
      - Commission to Review, Study and Reform Educational Leadership, HJR 124 (2004), 29 November 2004 (Box 131, Folder 4)
      - New Leaders for New Schools, 2004 (Box 131, Folder 5)
      - Made for the Middle, 2004 (Box 131, Folder 5)
      - Virginia Association of Secondary School Principals (VASSP) Meeting with Governor, 2 February 2005 (Box 131, Folder 5)
  - Subseries VI.E. Teachers, 2002-2005., Extent: 1.05 cubic feet. (Box 132-134)
    In May 2000 the Virginia State Board of Education and the State Council of Higher Education (SCHEV) for Virginia created the Joint Task Force on the K-12 Teaching Profession to develop a series of recommendations on issues facing the teaching profession in Virginia. The Joint Task Force presented its recommendations to the Board of Education and SCHEV in June 2001 and they recommended that a committee be established to continue the work of the task force. The Committee to Enhance the K-12 Teaching Profession in Virginia was established in February 2002 by the Virginia Board of Education and SCHEV to design a comprehensive blueprint for advancing the teaching profession in Virginia. The committee's work was complemented by Virginia's inclusion in the National Governors Association (NGA) Center for Best Practices State Policy Institute on Recruiting and Retaining High Quality Teachers for the Nation's Classrooms project and a three-year Teacher Quality Enhancement Grant from the United States Department of Education. Records in this series document the work of the Committee to Enhance the K-12 Teaching Profession in Virginia, the NGA project and the Teacher Quality Enhancement Grant.
    - Committee to Enhance the K-12 Teaching Profession in Virginia, 2002
      - Records, 2002 (part one) (Box 132, Folder 1)
      - Records, 2002 (part two) (Box 132, Folder 2)
      - Records, 2002 (part three) (Box 132, Folder 3)
      - Records, 2002 (part four) (Box 132, Folder 4)
      - Records, 2002 (part five) (Box 132, Folder 5)
    - Education Retreat, 2002
      - Education Retreat, 8-10 September 2002 (Box 133, Folder 1)
    - Board of Education, No Child Left Behind Reading Study, 2002
      - Board of Education, No Child Left Behind Committee Meeting, 6 November 2002 (Box 133, Folder 2)
      - Board of Education, No Child Left Behind, Reading Meeting, 4 October 2002 (Box 133, Folder 2)
      - Board of Education, No Child Left Behind, Reading Meeting, 4 September 2002 (Box 133, Folder 2)
    - NGA Teacher Quality Conference, Charlotte, North Carolina, 21-22 November 2002
      - Records, 2002 (part one) (Box 133, Folder 3)
      - Records, 2002 (part two) (Box 133, Folder 4)
    - Teacher Quality Enhancement Grant, 2002-2005
      - Grant Application, 2002 (part one) (Box 133, Folder 5)
      - Grant Application, 2002 (part two) (Box 133, Folder 6)
      - Grant Application, 2002 (part three) (Box 133, Folder 7)
      - Advisory Council on Teacher Quality, 31 March 2003 Meeting (Box 134, Folder 1)
      - Teacher Preparation Task Force, 22 May 2003 Meeting (Box 134, Folder 1)
      - Advisory Council on Teacher Quality, 26 June 2003 Meeting (Box 134, Folder 1)
      - Advisory Council on Teacher Quality, 11 December 2003 Meeting (Box 134, Folder 2)
      - Advisory Council on Teacher Quality, 22 June 2004 Meeting (Box 134, Folder 2)
      - Teacher Quality Enhancement Grant Advisory Council, 7 December 2005 Meeting (Box 134, Folder 2)
      - George Banks - Lead Teacher Model, Lancaster County, 2002 (Box 134, Folder 3)
      - Merit Pay/Standards Based Compensation, 2002 (Box 134, Folder 3)
      - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia (SCHEV), 2004-05 No Child Left Behind Grant Opportunities, December 2003 (Box 134, Folder 4)
      - Recruitment, VA REAP, no date (Box 134, Folder 4)
      - National Commission on Teaching and America's Future Conference, July 2004 (Box 134, Folder 4)
      - National Board for Professional Teaching Standards, 2003-2004 (Box 134, Folder 5)
      - Virginia Teachers for Tomorrow, 2003 (Box 134, Folder 5)
      - The Next Generation of Teachers: The Role of State Policymakers and Higher Education in Ensuring Quality, Conference, 3-4 February 2005 (Box 134, Folder 6)
  - Subseries VI.E. High School Reform, 2004-2005., Extent: 0.35 cubic feet. (Box 135)
    This subseries is housed in one boxe and is arranged roughly chronologically. In July 2005, the National Governors Association selected Virginia to receive an Honor States Program Grant as part of it's Redesigning the American High School Initiative. The NGA program, initiated by NGA Chairman and Virginia Governor Mark Warner, provides grants to implement redesign initiatives in high schools, specifically targeting high school graduation rates and increase college readiness. The records in this series document the Warner Administration's work on improving Virginia's high schools in 2004 and it's efforts to secure the grant from the NGA in 2005. Notable documents include "Virginia's Proposal to the National Governors Association to Redesign the American High School", dated 1 June 2005 (Box 135, Folder 5).
    - The Governor's High School Leadership Summit, 8 March 2004 (Box 135, Folder 1)
    - Southern Governors' Association, "New Traditions: Options for Rural High School Excellence", 23 July 2004 (part one) (Box 135, Folder 2)
    - Southern Governors' Association, "New Traditions: Options for Rural High School Excellence", 23 July 2004 (part two) (Box 135, Folder 3)
    - High School Reform Efforts, 2004-2005 (Box 135, Folder 4)
    - Redesigning the American High School Grant, 2005 (Box 135, Folder 5)
  - Subseries VI.G. Healthy Virginians, 2003-2005., Extent: 0.35 cubic feet. (Box 136)
    This subseries is housed in one box and is arranged roughly chronologically. In November 2004, Governor Warner launched the Healthy Virginians initiative, an effort to promote health and wellness and reduce health care costs by combating obesity, hypertension, and other preventable diseases among state employees, public school students, Medicaid recipients, and the public. The records in this subseries document the programs efforts at combating obesity in public schools.
    - School Health, 2003 (Box 136, Folder 1)
    - School Obesity - Food Research and Action Center (FRAC), 2004 (Box 136, Folder 2)
    - Healthy Virginians, 2005 (Box 136, Folder 3)
- VII. Additional Records (accession 44681), 1994; 1998; 2000-2006., Extent: 9.64 cubic feet (29 boxes). (Box 137-165)
  The records in this series were not part of the originial Warner administration Secretary of Education transfer in January 2006. For reasons unknown, they remained in the Secretary's office and were transferred to the Library in January 2010 as part of the Kaine administration collection. The Additional Records series is arranged into four subseries and is housed in 29 archival boxes. Subseries have been designated for: A. Correspondence and Supporting Documentation, Office of the Secretary; B. Special Projects and Studies; C. Legislative Files; and D. Weekly Reports. The deliniation between subseries A and B was not discernable by the processing archivist; researchers should check both subseries. The series consists of agendas, agreements, articles, background materials, briefing books, correspondence, e-mail, grants, handouts, legislation, lists, memorandum, notes, presentations, reports, studies, and surveys.
  - Subseries VII.A. Correspondence and Supporting Documentation, Office of the Secretary, 2001-2006., Extent: 5.95 cubic feet. (Box 137-153)
    This subseries is housed in 17 boxes. The processing archivist retained the original order of the files, but arranged them in alphabetical order in thle finding aid to facilitate better access. This subseries contains agendas, correspondence, background materials, e-mail (printed out), handouts, legislation, memorandum, notes, presentations, and reports. Included in this series are correspondence to/from Belle Wheelan (2002-2005) and Peter Blake (2005-2006). Researchers should check Series II. Assigned State Agencies, Series IV. Office of the Secretary, and Series VI. Special Projects for additional records.
    - Accomplishments, 2002; 2004. (Box 137, Folder 2)
    - An Achievable Dream, 2002-2003. (Box 138, Folder 5)
    - Advisory Council on the Future of Nursing, 2002; 2004-2005. (Box 138, Folder 5)
    - African American History (Kent Ruffin), 2003-2004. (Box 152, Folder 1)
    - Agency Head Executive Agreements, 2002. (Box 152, Folder 3)
    - Alliance for Execellent Education, 2004. (Box 138, Folder 5)
    - American Civil War Center, 2005. (Box 138, Folder 5)
    - America Competes Act, 2006-2008. (Box 138, Folder 5)
    - American Council on Education, 2004. (Box 138, Folder 5)
    - The Annie E. Casey Foundation 2006 Kids Count Data Book, 2006. (Box 137, Folder 1)
    - Ask Why, 2002. (Box 151, Folder 1)
    - Office of the Attorney General, 2002-2004. (Box 146, Folder 4)
    - Auditor of Public Accounts, 2005. (Box 139, Folder 1)
    - Auditor of Public Accounts, 2001; 2003-2005. (Box 146, Folder 2)
    - Autism Program of Virginia, 2003. (Box 139, Folder 1)
    - Awards, 2002-2004. (Box 152, Folder 1)
    - Boston Day and Evening Academy, 2006. (Box 137, Folder 4)
    - Brown v. Board of Education Scholarship, 2004-2005. (Box 152, Folder 1)
    - Cabinet Technology Team for Education and Technology, 2004. (Box 152, Folder 1)
    - Center for Education, 2002. (Box 145, Folder 6)
    - Chartwells Hospitality, 2003. (Box 139, Folder 1)
    - Coalition for Community Schools, 2003. (Box 139, Folder 1)
    - The College Board, 2002. (Box 144, Folder 6)
    - Committee to Enhance the K-12 Teaching Profession in Virginia, 2001. (Box 139, Folder 1)
    - Commonwealth of Virginia Campaign (CVC), 2002. (Box 151, Folder 3)
    - Assistant to the Governor for Commonwealth Preparedness, 2002-2005. (Box 148, Folder 6)
    - Comptroller's Office Correspondence, 2002-2005. (Box 146, Folder 6)
    - Conflice of Interests Act, 2002. (Box 139, Folder 1)
    - Congressional Delegation, 2002-2005. (Box 151, Folder 2)
    - Construction Taskforce, 2004. (Box 139, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 2004; 8 April 2005 - 21 November 2005. (Box 137, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 28 November 2005 - 11 January 2006. (Box 137, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence with Governor's Office, General Assembly, and Congress, 2002-2005. (Box 152, Folder 2)
    - Council on Virginia's Future, 2002-2003. (Box 137, Folder 5)
    - Council on Virginia's Future, 2005. (Box 137, Folder 6)
    - County Board of Supervisors, 2004. (Box 151, Folder 1)
    - Department for the Aging, 2004. (Box 146, Folder 3)
    - Department of Correctional Education, 2004. (Box 146, Folder 7)
    - Department of Emergency Management, 2004-2005. (Box 146, Folder 8)
    - Dept. of Emergency Services, 2003. (Box 139, Folder 1)
    - Department of Environmental Quality, 2004-2005. (Box 147, Folder 2)
    - Department of General Services, 2003-2005. (Box 147, Folder 3)
    - Dept. of General Services, 2004. (Box 139, Folder 1)
    - Department of Health, 2002-2003; 2005. (Box 147, Folder 5)
    - Department of Human Resource Management, 2004-2005. (Box 148, Folder 5)
    - Department of Mental Health, Mental Retardation and Substance Abuse Services, 2005. (Box 148, Folder 3)
    - Department of Mental Health, Mental Retardation and Substance Abuse Services, 2002-2004. (Box 148, Folder 4)
    - Department of Minority Business Enterprise, 2002-2004. (Box 147, Folder 1)
    - Department of Motor Vehicles, 2003. (Box 148, Folder 5)
    - Department of Planning and Budget, 2002-2005. (Box 148, Folder 7)
    - Department of Social Services, 2004. (Box 149, Folder 1)
    - Dept. of State Police, 2002. (Box 139, Folder 1)
    - Department of Technology Planning, 2002. (Box 149, Folder 3)
    - Virginia Department of Transportation, 2004. (Box 149, Folder 4)
    - Virginia Department of the Treasury, 2003. (Box 149, Folder 4)
    - Diversity Pipeline Alliance, 2003. (Box 139, Folder 1)
    - Education Commission of the States, 2004-2005. (Box 139, Folder 2)
    - Education Commission of the States, 2003-2004. (Box 139, Folder 3)
    - Education Commission of the States, 2003. (Box 139, Folder 4)
    - Ethics Resource Center, 2002-2003. (Box 144, Folder 6)
    - eVA, 2002. (Box 140, Folder 1)
    - Even Start, 2004-2005. (Box 140, Folder 2)
    - Fairfax County Chamber of Commerce, 2002. (Box 140, Folder 2)
    - Family Foundation, 2004. (Box 140, Folder 2)
    - First Robotics, 2002. (Box 149, Folder 1)
    - Foundation of Virginia, 2003. (Box 145, Folder 7)
    - 4-H, 2003. (Box 140, Folder 2)
    - Garfield F. Childs Memorial Fund, 2003. (Box 140, Folder 2)
    - General Assembly, 2004. (Box 151, Folder 1)
    - General Obligation Bond, 2002. (Box 145, Folder 1)
    - GEAR UP (Gaining Early Awareness and Readiness for Undergraduate Programs), 2002-2003. (Box 140, Folder 3)
    - Global Cultures, 2003. (Box 140, Folder 3)
    - Governor's Fellows, 2002. (Box 147, Folder 4)
    - Governor's Higher Education Summit Committee, 2002. (Box 145, Folder 2)
    - Governor's Office for Substance Abuse Prevention, 2002; 2004. (Box 149, Folder 1)
    - Governor's School for Science and Technology, 2002; 2004. (Box 145, Folder 6)
    - Governor's Task Force for Agriculture and Forestry, 2004. (Box 145, Folder 5)
    - Governor's Task Force on Efficiency and Effectiveness, 2002. (Box 151, Folder 1)
    - Governor's Task Force on Preventing Crime in Virginia's Minority Community, 2003. (Box 151, Folder 1)
    - GROW Network, 2004-2005. (Box 140, Folder 4)
    - HB 2404, 2003. (Box 151, Folder 1)
    - HB 675 (Home School), 2004. (Box 151, Folder 3)
    - Halifax Educational Foundation, 2005. (Box 140, Folder 5)
    - Healthy Virginia, 2002. (Box 140, Folder 5)
    - Homeland Security, 2002-2003; 2005. (Box 147, Folder 7)
    - House of Delegates, 2002-2003. (Box 147, Folder 6)
    - Institute for Advanced Learning and Research, 2001; 2005. (Box 140, Folder 5)
    - Jack Kent Cooke Foundation, 2003. (Box 140, Folder 5)
    - JLARC, 2002-2003. (Box 140, Folder 6)
    - Jobs for America's Graduates, 2002-2005. (Box 140, Folder 7)
    - Jobs for Virginia Graduates, 2002-2005. (Box 140, Folder 8)
    - Joint Commission on Health Care, 2003. (Box 148, Folder 1)
    - K-12 Workgroups, 2002. (Box 145, Folder 4)
    - Latitudes Group, 2004. (Box 151, Folder 3)
    - Legislative Briefings, 2002. (Box 148, Folder 2)
    - Legislative Services, 2002; 2004-2005. (Box 148, Folder 1)
    - Libraries, 2003-2004. (Box 145, Folder 6)
    - Office of the Lieutenant Governor, 2002. (Box 148, Folder 1)
    - Maggie Walker Governor's School, 2003. (Box 145, Folder 6)
    - Making a Wish Foundation, undated. (Box 145, Folder 6)
    - Martin Luther King Commission, 2004. (Box 151, Folder 5)
    - The McKenzie Group, 2004. (Box 151, Folder 5)
    - Meetings
      - Miscellaneous, 2002-2003, 2005. (Box 152, Folder 4)
      - Accountability Work Groups, 2002. (Box 152, Folder 4)
      - Cabinet Meetings, 2004-2005. (Box 152, Folder 4)
      - Commonwealth Educational Policy Institute, 2002. (Box 152, Folder 4)
      - Electronic Campus of Virginia, 2002. (Box 152, Folder 5)
      - Fairfax County Federation of Teachers, 2002. (Box 152, Folder 5)
      - FAMIS, 2002. (Box 152, Folder 5)
      - IBM, 2002. (Box 152, Folder 5)
      - Immigration, 2002-2003. (Box 152, Folder 6)
      - No Child Left Behind, 2002-2004. (Box 152, Folder 7)
      - Siemens, 2002. (Box 153, Folder 1)
      - Southern Regional Education Board, 2002. (Box 153, Folder 1)
      - TekXam, 13 June 2002. (Box 153, Folder 1)
      - Virginia's Center for Innovative Technology, 2002-2005. (Box 153, Folder 2)
      - Virginia House Joint Resolution 170 (Commission on Access and Diversity in Higher Education), 19 July 2002. (Box 153, Folder 3)
      - Virginia House Joint Resolution 159 (Joint Subcommmittee to Study the Operations, Practices, Duties, and Funding of the Commonwealth's Agencies, Boards, Commissions, Councils, and other Government Entities) 2002. (Box 153, Folder 4)
    - MGT of American Final Reports (volumes)
      - Dinwiddie County Public Schools, School Division Efficiency Review, 23 March 2006. (Box 141)
      - Lancaster County Public Schools, School Division Efficiency Review, 17 March 2006. (Box 142)
      - Smyth County Public Schools, School Division Efficiency Review, 16 March 2006. (Box 142)
      - Winchester Public Schools, School Division Efficiency Review, 24 March 2006. (Box 142)
      - York County School Division, School Division Efficiency Review, 24 March 2006. (Box 142)
    - Ms. Wheelchair Virginia, 2003-2004. (Box 141, Folder 1)
    - NAB (National Alliance of Business), 2003. (Box 141, Folder 1)
    - NAGB (National Assessment Governing Board), 2003. (Box 141)
    - NASA, 2002. (Box 141, Folder 1)
    - NAEP (National Assessment of Educational Progress), 2003-2004. (Box 141, Folder 2)
    - National Governors Association, 2004. (Box 141, Folder 3)
    - New College of Virginia, 2004. (Box 139, Folder 7)
    - Nursing, 2004. (Box 141, Folder 3)
    - Office for Civil Rights, 2004. (Box 151, Folder 3)
    - Olmstead Initiative, 2002; 2004. (Box 151, Folder 6)
    - Patrick County Education Foundation (former Governor Gerald Baliles), 2004-2005. (Box 151, Folder 4)
    - Progressive Policy Institute, 2002-2003. (Box 141, Folder 3)
    - Project Lead the Way Evaluations, January 2003. (Box 140, Folder 9)
    - Public Education Consortium, 2002. (Box 145, Folder 6)
    - Amherst County Public Schools, 2004. (Box 145, Folder 5)
    - Chesapeake Public Schools, 2002. (Box 145, Folder 5)
    - Danville Public Schools, 2005. (Box 145, Folder 5)
    - Montgomery County Public Schools, 2002. (Box 145, Folder 5)
    - Newport News Public Schools, 2002. (Box 145, Folder 5)
    - Page County Public Schools, 2002. (Box 145, Folder 5)
    - Richmond City Public Schools, 2002; 2004-2005. (Box 145)
    - Race to GED, 2004. (Box 141, Folder 3)
    - Ron Brown Scholar Program, 2003. (Box 141, Folder 3)
    - Secretary of Administration, 2002-2005. (Box 146, Folder 1)
    - Secretary of Commerce and Trade, 2002; 2004. (Box 146, Folder 5)
    - Secretary of Education Strategic Plans, 2004-2006 Biennium
      - James Monroe Museum and Memorial Library, 31 July 2003. (Box 138, Folder 1)
      - Frontier Culture Museum, May-August 2003. (Box 138, Folder 1)
      - Science Museum of Virginia, August 2003. (Box 138, Folder 1)
      - Roanoke Higher Education Authority, June 2003; August 2003. (Box 138, Folder 1)
      - Virginia Department of Education, 21 May 2003; 8 August 2003. (Box 138, Folder 1)
      - Gunston Hall, 14 May 2003; 8 August 2003. (Box 138, Folder 2)
      - Southwest Virginia Higher Education Center, 16 June 2003; 8 August 2003. (Box 138, Folder 2)
      - Virginia Institute of Marine Sciences, May-August 2003. (Box 138, Folder 2)
      - Commission for the Arts, June 2003; August 2003. (Box 138, Folder 2)
      - State Council of Higher Education, May-June 2003. (Box 138, Folder 2)
      - Library of Virginia, May 2003; August 2003. (Box 138, Folder 2)
      - Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, May-June 2003. (Box 138, Folder 3)
      - Jefferson National Accelerator Facility, May-June 2003. (Box 138, Folder 3)
      - Christopher Newport University, August 2003. (Box 138, Folder 3)
      - Richard Bland College, undated. (Box 138, Folder 3)
      - Jamestown-Yorktown Foundation, May 2003; August 2003. (Box 138, Folder 4)